{"id":34,"text":"All India Institute of Medical Sciences (AIIMS) is the kind of healthcare services India should aspire for in its march to become a USD 3 trillion economy and a developed country, Prime Minister Narendra Modi said in Rajkot Sunday.","label":[[0,39,"ORG"],[41,46,"ORG"],[83,88,"GPE"],[132,147,"MONEY"],[195,208,"PERSON"],[217,223,"GPE"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":35,"text":"It is not often that a hockey match ends 4-0 with four different goal-scorers and the Player of the Match award goes to someone other than them.","label":[],"Comments":[]}
{"id":36,"text":"Maharashtra Chief Minister Eknath Shinde on Sunday cautioned Maratha quota activist Manoj Jarange Patil to not “cross his limits” after the latter alleged that Deputy Chief Minister Devendra Fadnavis was conspiring to “eliminate” him.","label":[[0,11,"GPE"],[27,41,"PERSON"],[84,103,"PERSON"],[182,199,"PERSON"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":37,"text":"If Gujarat looked toothless, Mumbai played the assertive brand of cricket which won them the trophy last year.","label":[[3,10,"GPE"],[29,35,"GPE"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":38,"text":"As per the January 31 order, the RBI asked PPBL to stop further deposits, credit transactions, or top-ups in any customer accounts, prepaid instruments, wallets, FASTags, and National Common Mobility Cards, after February 29.","label":[[11,21,"DATE"],[33,36,"ORG"],[43,47,"ORG"],[162,169,"ORG"],[213,224,"DATE"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":39,"text":"Students from SJD-run hostels in different parts of the state are now joining from their local level by raising the same issues with local authorities.","label":[[13,17,"ORG"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":40,"text":"All his hard work looked to be paying off – from renting a house in Vadodara, to trying to play junior cricket there.","label":[[68,76,"GPE"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":41,"text":"Solanki later revealed how the partnership would have taken them to a safe zone.","label":[[0,7,"PERSON"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":42,"text":"Fearing for his safety, the NRI digitally transferred Rs 98,000.","label":[[54,63,"MONEY"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":43,"text":"On the fourth day, India could complete a famous come-from-behind series win.","label":[[19,24,"GPE"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":44,"text":"The number of visitors on the first day on Saturday was around 70,000 which included around 20,000 students.","label":[[63,69,"CARDINAL"],[92,98,"CARDINAL"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":45,"text":"It’s as valid as Western ideas that privileges institutions or a document or a God\/state over any leader.","label":[],"Comments":[]}
{"id":46,"text":"Sunak believes that this sends a dangerous message that intimidation is effective.","label":[[0,5,"PERSON"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":47,"text":"Xiaomi launched its budget smartphone — Redmi 13C in India in December last year.","label":[[0,6,"ORG"],[40,49,"PRODUCT"],[53,58,"GPE"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":48,"text":"Nafe Singh Rathee, the Haryana chief of the Indian National Lok Dal, was allegedly shot dead by unidentified assailants in Bahadurgarh.","label":[[0,17,"PERSON"],[23,30,"GPE"],[60,67,"NORP"],[123,134,"GPE"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":49,"text":"Demanding a CBI inquiry, senior INLD leader Abhay Chautala said that Rathee was shot dead in Jhajjar district.","label":[[12,15,"ORG"],[32,36,"ORG"],[44,58,"PERSON"],[69,75,"PERSON"],[93,99,"GPE"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":50,"text":"A doctor was brutally attacked inside a hospital in Maharashtra on Friday night.","label":[[52,63,"GPE"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":51,"text":"Our Hon CM has already send Help.. and necessary steps are being taken for the welfare of the people.","label":[],"Comments":[]}
{"id":52,"text":"In his speech, Rahul Gandhi raised the issue of unemployment and pointed out that he saw young men lying on the road drunk in Varanasi.","label":[[14,27,"PERSON"],[126,134,"GPE"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":53,"text":"n landscapes modified by human activity, the Indian wolf may be adapting by suppressing their iconic howl, finds a 2023 study from Maharashtra.","label":[[45,51,"NORP"],[131,142,"GPE"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":54,"text":"Shahani directed a number of acclaimed films including Maya Darpan, Char Adhyay and Kasba.","label":[[0,7,"PERSON"],[55,66,"WORK_OF_ART"],[68,79,"WORK_OF_ART"],[84,89,"WORK_OF_ART"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":55,"text":"“I fear we are on the edge of a monumental disaster with grave implications for regional peace, security and human rights,” he added.","label":[],"Comments":[]}
{"id":56,"text":"Mr. Sayani was one of the most recognizable voices in Indian radio as the host of one of the first radio shows in the country.","label":[[0,10,"PERSON"],[92,98,"ORDINAL"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":57,"text":"Rakesh Sihag, the head of the INLD's media cell, confirmed Nafe Singh Rathi's death in the shootout.","label":[[0,12,"PERSON"],[30,34,"ORG"],[59,77,"PERSON"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":58,"text":"Analysis of the data revealed that on average, 600 people become victims of dog bites in Bihar every day.","label":[[89,94,"GPE"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":59,"text":"In Karnataka, home delivery of foodgrains for residents aged 90 and above brings hope, security.","label":[[3,12,"GPE"],[61,63,"CARDINAL"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":60,"text":"A good memoir, like writer Amitava Kumar’s ‘The Yellow Book’, creates a sense of collective belonging and togetherness.","label":[[27,40,"PERSON"],[44,59,"WORK_OF_ART"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":61,"text":"Renowned filmmaker Kumar Shahani passes away at 83.","label":[[19,32,"PERSON"],[48,50,"CARDINAL"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":62,"text":"Deshwal leads the raid points charts with 262 points and 16 Super 10s.","label":[[0,7,"ORG"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":63,"text":"Proteins found in the plasma are biological markers for the changes that occur in dementia sufferers over a decade before clinical symptoms appear.","label":[],"Comments":[]}
{"id":64,"text":"Help fund the most diverse Lok Sabha election coverage in 2024.","label":[[27,36,"ORG"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":65,"text":"Every week, Eco India brings you stories that inspire you to build a cleaner, greener and better tomorrow.","label":[[12,21,"ORG"]],"Comments":[]}
